webloggerz.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Webloggerz

You are here: [Home](http://webloggerz.com/) » Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy Document for Web Loggerz

**Hi there! Welcome to Web Loggerz.**

**webloggerz.com** respects your privacy and **at Web Loggerz, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance**. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by webloggerz.com and how it is used.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of webloggerz.com.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates.

Our main primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safer browsing experience.

### Tracking:

When you visit this website, we can record certain information in relation to your visit such as:

  * Your IP or proxy server IP
  * Basic domain information
  * Your Internet service provider is sometimes captured depending on the configuration of your ISP connection
  * The date and time of your visit to the website
  * The length of your session
  * The pages which you have accessed
  * The number of times you access our site within any month
  * The size of the file you look at
  * The website which referred you to our website
  * The operating system which your computer uses.

This is done by making use of analytical softwares such as Google Analytics, Bing Webmasters primarily for the data analysis and web development process and we do not share this with any third-party.

### Cookies:

We do make use of session cookies, which are used only during a browsing session, and expire as soon you quit your browser.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookies can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Publishing Policy

webloggerzs.com favors high-quality, neutral, unbiased and only original work by each author.

We accept well-written, knowledge-powered, original articles from tech writers, designers and developers and intense care is being taken for not allowing any copied content to be republished or copied images to be re-posted on our website.

### User Comments:

Webloggerz.com allows users to comment on the site. However, we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion.  
While commenting on this site please refrain from using content that is not suitable. Your email address mentioned while posting new comments can be used to send you promotional letters or new posts.

### Disclaimer

This Site contains links to other sites. Underlined words and phrases are click-through links or hyperlinks to pages and websites.

This document applies only to this website. Webloggerz is not responsible for the privacy practices of linked sites.

All pages and graphics on this website are the property of the company Webloggerz.

Reproduction or redistribution of the content in the form of text or graphics will be a violation of copyright laws.

**For any other information regarding our privacy policy, please[Contact Us](http://webloggerz.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us")**

_(This document was last updated on: 12 March 2014.)_
